That here just a few hours ago the Chief has announced
and here from Mandsaur and the
profit here which I have not subscribed
[music]
Ajay has
told under the bottle here the egg is on a
basis of 13.1 percent and here
cnbc-awaaz 6 crore subscribed and here
you subscribe subscribed
next we have
26 crore inverter information so a
sticker and here here you can see
here it is below 600 but there here let's
go here
things to pay attention here the President Focus
Deposit Liquid Dabang Dabang-2
press here so that it is good in
a group from inside take it on book increase
by 15.6 transplant year basis ₹2 dry
10.82 lakh crore and deposit by 19.5
versus loot 0.06 subscribe and here and here
and subscribed here also
it is so interesting up you
can see here
tilak gave money on December 08  If I gave you money for that, then
I told you that the money that you raised from here,
okay, you gave one lakh rupees to someone for
₹40, that last 500 subscribers, if you do
n't want to have any problem,
please watch the video, watch it and take it, you
don't have to do anything, you have to subscribe and
like this video com and here
if any of your girls have been saved then please comment,
we will do it in the next video, till then
bye-bye